A Guide to the Papers of the Office of the Vice President for Student Affairs ca. 1969-2001
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the Office of the Vice President for Student Affairs ca. 1969-2001
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-18/2/1.031
This collection consists of the papers from the Office of the Vice President for Student Affairs (formerly the Dean of Students), ca. 1969-2001, ca. 1,000 items ( 5 Hollinger boxes, linear shelf feet).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access is prohibited to the judiciary and honor committee material (all material in Boxes 3-5) by anyone other than members of the Judiciary Committee or the Honor Committee or its secretary, and then only with written permission of the president of the Honor Committee or the president of the Judiciary Committee or his properly authorized representative.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the University of Virginia Library by Brent Evans, Office of the Vice President for Student Affairs, Rotunda, University of Virginia, on August 28, 2003.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of the papers from the Office of the Vice President for Student Affairs (formerly the Dean of Students), ca. 1969-2001, ca. 1,000 items ( 5 Hollinger boxes, linear shelf feet). Among the papers are annual reports sent to the Vice President for Student Affairs including the Office of Financial Aid to Students, Foreign Student Advisor, Office of Career Planning and Placement, Office of Registrar, Newcomb Hall and University Union, Office of the Dean of Students, Office of the Dean of Women, Department of Student Health, Office of Afro-American Affairs, Office of Admissions, all arranged by year.
Also present are International Center and Counseling Center proposals; student Judiciary Committee papers; and Honor Committee correspondence and files.
Contents List
- Annual Reports 1969 (Box-folder 1:1)
- Annual Reports 1970 (Box-folder 1:2)
- Annual Reports 1971 (Box-folder 1:3)
- Annual Reports 1972-1973 (Box-folder 1:4)
- Annual Reports 1972-1973 (Box-folder 1:5)
- Annual Reports 1972-1973 (Box-folder 1:6)
- Annual Reports 1976 (Box-folder 1:7)
- Annual Reports 1976 (Box-folder 1:8)
- Annual Reports 1977 (Box-folder 1:9)
- Annual Reports 1977 (Box-folder 1:10)
- Annual Reports 1977 (Box-folder 1:11)
- Annual Reports 1979 (Box-folder 1:12)
- Annual Reports 1979-1980 (Box-folder 1:13)
- Annual Reports 1979-1980 (Box-folder 1:14)
- Annual Reports 1979-1980 (Box-folder 1:15)
- Annual Reports 1980-1981 (Box-folder 2:1)
- Annual Reports 1980-1981 (Box-folder 2:2)
- Annual Reports 1980-1981 (Box-folder 2:3)
- Annual Reports 1981-1982 (Box-folder 2:4)
- Annual Reports 1981-1982 (Box-folder 2:5)
- Annual Reports 1981-1982 (Box-folder 2:6)
- Annual Reports 1981-1982 (Box-folder 2:7)
- Annual Reports 1981-1982 (Box-folder 2:8)
- Annual Reports - Office of Afro-American Affairs 1979-1980 (Box-folder 2:9)
- Annual Reports - Office of Afro-American Affairs 1980-1981 (Box-folder 2:10)
- Annual Reports - Department of Student Health 1978-1979 (Box-folder 2:11)
- Department of Student Health - Proposal for Realignment of the Counseling Center and LNEC 1996 (Box-folder 2:12)
- Department of Student Health - Proposal for Realignment of the Counseling Center and LNEC 1996 (Box-folder 2:13)
- International Center 1977-1979 (Box-folder 2:14)
- International Center 1982-1988 (Box-folder 2:15)
- International Center 1991-1998 (Box-folder 2:16)
- Honor Committee Correspondence (Restricted) 1988 (Box-folder 3:1)
- Honor Committee Correspondence (Restricted) 1989 (Box-folder 3:2)
- Honor Committee Correspondence (Restricted) 1990 (Box-folder 3:3)
- Honor Committee Correspondence (Restricted) 1991 (Box-folder 3:4)
- Honor Committee Correspondence (Restricted) 1992 (Box-folder 3:5)
- Honor Committee Correspondence (Restricted) 1993 (Box-folder 3:6)
- Honor Committee Correspondence (Restricted) 1993 (Box-folder 3:7)
- Honor Committee Correspondence (Restricted) 1994 (Box-folder 3:8)
- Honor Committee Correspondence (Restricted) 1994 (Box-folder 3:9)
- Honor Committee (Restricted) 1994 (Box-folder 3:10)
- Honor Committee (Restricted) 1994 (Box-folder 3:11)
- Honor Committee (Restricted) 1994 (Box-folder 3:12)
- Honor Committee Correspondence (Restricted) 1995 (Box-folder 4:1)
- Honor Committee Correspondence (Restricted) 1996 (Box-folder 4:2)
- Honor Committee Correspondence (Restricted) 1996 (Box-folder 4:3)
- Judicial Cases (Restricted) 1993 (Box-folder 4:4)
- Judicial Cases (Restricted) 1993 (Box-folder 4:5)
- Judicial Cases (Restricted) 1993 (Box-folder 4:6)
- Judicial Cases (Restricted) 1993 (Box-folder 4:7)
- Judicial Cases (Restricted) 1994 (Box-folder 4:8)
- Judicial Cases (Restricted) 1994 (Box-folder 4:9)
- Judicial Cases (Restricted) 1994 (Box-folder 5:1)
- Judicial Cases (Restricted) 1994 (Box-folder 5:2)
- Judicial Cases (Restricted) 1995 (Box-folder 5:3)
- Judicial Cases (Restricted) 1995 (Box-folder 5:4)
- Judicial Cases (Restricted) 1995 (Box-folder 5:5)
- Judicial Cases (Restricted) 1996 (Box-folder 5:6)
- Judicial Cases (Restricted) 1996 (Box-folder 5:7)
- Judicial Cases (Restricted) 1996 (Box-folder 5:8)
- Judicial Cases (Restricted) 1996 (Box-folder 5:9)
- University Judiciary Committee Correspondence (Restricted) 1993 (Box-folder 5:10)
- University Judiciary Committee Correspondence (Restricted) 1994 (Box-folder 5:11)
- University Judiciary Committee Correspondence (Restricted) 1995 (Box-folder 5:12)